He's crying, Kajan.
That's enough.
If you bother him again, I won't leave
you.
Powerless kid.
So you're pretending to be a hero again.
Kajan.
We weren't born the same way.
When I was four years old, that's when
I found out about this bitter truth.
But this obstacle was the first and last
for me.
Wow!
What a big villain!
It all started in KK City, China.
The news of a shining kid came out.
Since then, such strange kids were seen everywhere.
No one knew why.
But soon, these strange powers became commonplace.
Stories became reality.
Today, 80% of the population has a
superpower.
Now, there are such people everywhere.
In this chaotic world, a new job has
begun.
A dream that humans have always dreamt of.
And that job is...
This is Death Arms.
A hero who uses his powerful hands to
bring justice to the people.
Stop!
Don't go ahead!
There could be danger ahead!
Move back!
What's going on?
Why did you save us from the backdrop?
The ability to turn into such a big
monster?
What an amazing energy, right?
What did he do?
A loot.
He's going crazy because he's trapped.
Such a powerful energy.
He's still a criminal.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
But I don't think I'll be able to
come to work on time today.
Run!
Go away!
Who is Connor fighting?
Kamui Bull!
The rising star who has become famous.
You're answering your own questions, kid.
Are you a fanboy?
No.
No!
You used your power during the rush hour
and looted it.
You will be punished for this.
His power!
You should have taught him a lesson, Mr.
Tree Man!
Strike!
Chain!
Can you turn on?
He's here!
He's the take for the world's next hottest
hero.
Hi there everyone, I'm Mount Lady.
And you don't have to worry about this
bum anymore.
Money shot!
All my hard work has gone down the
drain.
Because of the rise of superpowers, criminal activities
also increased.
Where the government was making new laws for
the sake of power.
But on the other hand, there were such
brave people who risked their lives to protect
the city.
Just like the heroes in comic books.
They were using their powers to save us
from the criminals.
And because they got a lot of public
support, they started working to keep the government
in peace.
Those who performed well are also given the
first rank along with payment.
Their career depends on how famous and great
they are.
Gigantification.
This is a great and unprecedented power that
has been used here.
Although if you look at the condition of
these roads, I don't think it should be
used much.
But I don't know if it will be
able to control its size or not.
And you are making notes?
You also want to be a hero?
That's right.
All the best.
Thank you so much.
Izuku Midoriya.
Origin.
Now you are third year students.
It's time for you to think about your
future.
So now I'm going to give you all
an ambition form.
But what's the use?
I know you all want to be heroes.
You all have great power.
But it is forbidden to use it in
school.
Sir, please don't compare me with these idiots.
I'm not like these losers at all.
None of this is ahead of me, sir.
Heroes, what are you doing?
You should remember this place, side heroes.
Yes, I remember that Baku wants to go
to UA High.
UA High?
UA High is my exam this year.
Every year the competition is more difficult.
That's why you can't compare me.
I have got an A in mock exam.
I am the only one whose result fulfills
the requirement.
I swear that I will become a more
powerful hero than All Might.
And my name will be at the top
of the list of the highest taxpayers.
I remember.
Midoriya also wants to go to UA High.
Midoriya, don't stop.
Being good at studies doesn't mean that you
can become a hero.
There is no such rule.
Anyone can become a hero.
Hey, Deku.
You can't become anything.
You don't even have any power.
How can you think that you are equal
to me?
No, no.
Please stop, Kachchan.
I don't want to compete with you.
I am telling the truth.
This has been the only purpose of my
life since childhood.
And if I don't try, how will I
know?
What do you mean you won't try?
You die in the exams.
Do you have any super power?
You are of no use.
Someone help me.
If you can catch me, catch me.
It's very strange.
No hero has come.
Usually, a hero comes.
He has taken advantage of the right opportunity
to rob.
Everywhere Deku goes, people of power are unemployed.
This will never end.
It will end.
Ask me why?
Because I have come.
I have come.
Hey, how about karaoke?
This is the only option left.
Whatever happened this morning has come in the
news.
I should go back there and prepare my
notes.
Our conversation is not over yet, Deku.
Raj, what is this in your hand?
Hero analysis for the future?
Are you kidding, Midoriya?
That's enough.
Please return me.
But why?
First class superheroes look different.
Even if they are students.
Why not?
I will go to the U.A. High
School.
School before the rest of the students.
Everyone knows this.
If you want, you can call me a
perfectionist.
So much ego.
Remember one thing, Deku.
You will not go to the U.A.
High School.
Understood?
Hey.
Dude.
At least save yourself.
Let him go.
He is mad.
He cannot face the reality.
If you really want to be a hero,
you have only one way.
Pray to God that you also get some
power.
And then jump off the roof immediately.
Any problem?
Idiot.
If you have power, you don't know what
you think of yourself.
Think before you speak.
Don't eat it.
Idiot.
This is my notebook.
Hungry fish.
Idiot.
I will...
Mom.
Come on.
Computer.
Hurry up.
Oh.
You have already given 10,000 views to
these people.
You should not look at the computer so
much.
This is a very old video.
There was an accident at that time.
And this video was about the arrival of
a hero after that accident.
Did you see?
He has saved 100 people so far.
That too in just 10 minutes.
Amazing.
He is laughing.
Laughing.
Don't be afraid.
Ask me why?
Because I have come.
He is so cool.
Once my power is awakened, I will become
a hero like him.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, kids.
This is not possible.
What do you mean?
Something must have gone wrong.
All the kids in kindergarten are ready.
Except him.
I'm sorry.
But ma'am, you are from the fourth
generation, right?
Can I know your powers?
I have a little telekinetic power.
And my husband...
He spits fire.
I should have seen a combination of one
or two of these powers in Izuku by
now.
But looking at his X-ray, it seems
that this will not happen.
When superpowers began to be seen in people,
a lot of research was done on them.
And doctors found out the link between the
bones of their legs and the possibility of
superpowers in them.
The people who have powers have a joint
in the little finger of their leg.
Their bodies are more developed than the bodies
of ordinary people.
As you can see, Izuku has two joints
in his finger.
Which is found in 20% of people
today.
According to the research, it is certain that
your son will not have any powers.
Did you see?
He has saved 100 people so far.
And that too in just 10 minutes.
He did a great job.
Don't be afraid.
Forgive me.
No.
I didn't want to hear this, Mom.
I wish you had said at that time
that...
You have made up your mind, right?
Then it's okay.
You don't need to listen to anyone.
Keep your head up and keep moving forward.
Mom.
Belette.
Where is she?
I told you to keep quiet.
Don't worry.
I'm just taking over your body.
It will be easier for both of us
if you don't fight back.
It'll only hurt for a minute.
You'll feel better soon!
I can't breathe.
Grab all you want.
My body's made of fluid.
Thanks for the help.
You're a real hero to me, kid.
I didn't know he was in this.
I gotta get out of here fast before
he tracks me down.
My body is fluid.
I think I'm dying.
No, it can't be the end.
Somebody...
Don't be afraid, kid.
I'm here.
X-Men!
The Superpower!
All right.
Hey!
I'm glad you're awake.
I'm glad you're alive.
Please excuse me.
You're stuck in this mess because of me.
I don't usually make such mistakes.
I was on vacation, and this area is
new to me, so...
so this happened.
But thank you very much.
Your bottle came in handy.
I'm number one hero.
All right.
He's here.
Look, he's here.
He's standing right in front of me.
I can't believe it.
He's there.
Look, he's there.
But where am I?
Where am I?
In my notebook.
I got it right first.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'll never forget this.
Thank you for saving my life.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Now I'm going to take him to the
police.
I'll see you on TV.
See you.
What's this?
You're leaving?
Professionals always have a plan.
Whether it's the villain or time.
Wait a minute.
I still have to ask him a lot
of questions.
See you again, kids.
Thank you for saving my life.
What are you doing?
Leave me.
You're after me.
If I let you go, I'll die.
You're right.
I have to ask you a lot of
questions.
I want an answer.
Okay.
I understand.
Now close your eyes and mouth.
It was terrible.
Okay.
I'll go down and send someone.
They'll let you go.
I don't have time for nonsense.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
I...
No.
I don't have time.
But...
Sorry, kids.
But it's not possible.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Do you have any superpower?
You're useless.
Yes.
I don't have any superpower.
But...
I think...
I'm still...
Can anyone become a superhero without a superpower?
Can anyone become a hero like you without
a superpower?
I can't believe it.
After that meeting with All Might, my life
will change so much.
At that time, I had no idea about
it.
Next episode.
I'm here.
What?
That villain ran away from the jail.
He's making a boy a bandit and creating
a ruckus on the street.
But my superpower time is going to end.
You're gone, All Might.
Is there a hero?
What's the need to be a hero?
Heroes always give their all.
The passion to go beyond the limits.
Dash Mantra.